<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ministries on Universal</title>
    <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/ministry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ministries on Universal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 15:12:46 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/ministry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ministries at HCC</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/ministry/women/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 15:12:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/ministry/women/</guid>
      <description>Women&amp;rsquo;s Ministry Women’s Ministry Poster Women’s Ministry Spring Cleaning for the Heart and Soul  SAT, April 13 1:30 pm – 3:30 pm HCC Chapel  Spring time means Spring Cleaning, but it can go far beyond the nooks and crannies of our homes. Join us as we explore what it means to declutter our hearts and refresh our souls. We will also have a time of fellowship and soap-crafting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ministries at HCC</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/ministry/singles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 15:12:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/ministry/singles/</guid>
      <description>Singles Vision To be a ministry within HCC for singles of all ages to grow through intimate communion with Jesus and genuine relationships with each other.
Mission To provide Christ-centered community by fostering grace-filled mentoring relationships and friendships by teaching about God’s good design for singleness and marriage, and topics including faith in the workplace and financial stewardship.
Connect Launch  Time: Saturday, January 26, 2019 6 – 8pm (To enable participants to have dinner on their own afterwards) Speaker: Pastor Jason Venue: HCC Chapel  Join us as we kickoff the new Connect ministry!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ministries at HCC</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/ministry/family-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 15:12:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/ministry/family-life/</guid>
      <description> Family Life Save the Date – Square Dance
 Saturday, June 1 3:00pm – 5:00pm Chapel Free admission  HCC Family Life would like to invite yall to a square dance afternoon. All ages and all congregations are welcome. Admission is free. Please register so we know how many to expect.
 Register for HCC Square DanceHCC Square Dance </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ministries at HCC</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/ministry/youth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 15:11:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/ministry/youth/</guid>
      <description>HCC.YM - The Youth Ministry of Houston Chinese Church HCC.YM is a ministry by youth, with family, as the church that exists for the sole purpose of helping youth and their families become God-loving and compassionate disciples of Jesus Christ.
ENTER . ENGAGE . INVOLVE We help you – teenager, mom, dad, or guardian – become a disciple of Jesus by inviting you to enter the family of God. In everything we do, the good news of Jesus stands at the center, and we hope that you&amp;rsquo;ll choose to trust Him as you get to know Him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ministries at HCC</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/ministry/children/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 15:11:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/ministry/children/</guid>
      <description>Children&amp;rsquo;s Ministry Our passion at HCC is to connect kids and their families to God and others. We do this through worship, teaching, caring, serving, and outreach, striving to lay a spiritual foundation in their lives that will lead them to a personal relationship with Jesus Christ in God’s perfect timing. We also desire to provide them with a safe and nurturing environment where their faith can grow and blossom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ministries at HCC</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/ministry/nursery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 15:11:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/ministry/nursery/</guid>
      <description>Nursery ministry The Nursery ministry is for infants and toddlers age 0-3 years old. We provide a warm and welcoming environment where we hope children are drawn to learn about God and encouraged to pursue Him. Even young toddlers can learn that Jesus loves them. Our classes include 30 minutes of songs and stories centered on Christ. For more information about our ministry, please view our Nursery Brochure.
We’d love to hear from you at nursery@hcchome.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>