<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Group on Universal</title>
    <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/group/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Group on Universal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 13:52:16 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/group/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Groups at HCC</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/group/family/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 13:52:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/group/family/</guid>
      <description>Family Groups Our family groups provide a great context for building relationships and learning with and from each other. The frequency and format vary among groups, but we all share a commitment to mutually caring for each other. Groups that meet on Friday evenings at HCC offer opportunities for your kids through AWANA (children) and inSpire (teens).
If you are interested in visiting a group, please email smallgroups@hcchome.org expressing your interest along with a description of your life-stage and the age of your children (if applicable).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Groups at HCC</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/group/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 13:52:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/group/community/</guid>
      <description>Community Groups Community groups are open to people across various life stages. The vision is to foster gospel community among members who live, work, and play in a similar geographic community.
We believe a mix of singles, couples, and families (including kids) all in the same group will naturally encourage discipleship between older and younger believers. And if we&amp;rsquo;re all neighbors, then we can more easily and effectively reach our neighbors and serve our community together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Groups at HCC</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/group/colledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 13:40:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/group/colledge/</guid>
      <description>Cornerstone Christian Fellowship (CCF) Cornerstone Christian Fellowship is our collegiate fellowship that ministers to undergraduate students. We meet in co-ed small groups on Friday evenings in various locations on the Rice University campus. Meetings involve a shared meal, a dedicated time to study scripture, good conversation, and plenty of prayer.
If you would like more information about CCF or would like to visit a small group, email ccf@hcchome.org or join our Facebook group.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>