<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Universal</title>
    <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Universal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 15:19:06 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PayPal Giving Fund</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/about/donation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 15:19:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/about/donation/</guid>
      <description>Donation The nice thing is that with PPGF there are no fees to either you or to HCC for using a credit card to fund your donation – 100% of your donation will go to HCC.
If you would like to make an offering donation to HCC’s General Fund, please go to https://www.paypal.com/fundraiser/charity/1917834. Leave the Name and Email address box checked if you want us to also show your donations on your Annual HCC Offering Record to be emailed late next January.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staff @ HCC</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/about/staff/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 06:15:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/about/staff/</guid>
      <description>Christ is our Chief Shepherd (1 Pet. 5:4) and yet he has also gifted our church with undershepherds (Eph. 4:11) and other administrative staff for the purpose of equipping our members for the work of ministry and advancing our mission to make God-loving and compassionate disciples of Jesus among the nations.
Ministerial Staff John Smith Executive Pastor
111-222-3333 ext.100
 Email me
David Ben English Pastor
111-222-3333 ext.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/about/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 03:53:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/about/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you want to join in our worship? Please feel free to contact us, our customer service center is working for you 24&amp;frasl;7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Core Values</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/about/core-values/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 03:48:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/about/core-values/</guid>
      <description>Our Core Values All of our ministries at Houston Chinese Church are shaped by these twelve core values. By God&amp;rsquo;s grace, we seek to live out these values personally and corporately for His glory and the good of His church.
Christ&amp;rsquo;s Headship We acknowledge Christ as the head of our church. (Col 1:17-18)
Biblically Faithful We strive to teach God&amp;rsquo;s Word with integrity and authority to help individuals find Christ and live as his disciples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission &amp; Beliefs</title>
      <link>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/about/mission-beliefs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 03:45:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cainmagi.github.io/hugo-templates/hugo-universal/about/mission-beliefs/</guid>
      <description>Why We Exist Houston Chinese Church exists to make God-loving and compassionate disciples of Jesus Christ among all nations.
To this end, we commit ourselves to: God-exalting worship, Bible-centered teaching, Servant-minded caring, Spirit-led service, and Mission-driven outreach.
What We Believe  God is self-existent, creator of heaven and earth, and of all mankind. He is the only true God-Father, Son and Holy Spirit, three in one. Jesus Christ is the only begotten Son of God, the Word incarnate, conceived by the Holy Spirit, born of the virgin Mary.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>